<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Olivia Weng</title>
    <link>http://oliviaweng.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Olivia Weng</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 19:19:44 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://oliviaweng.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>On taking walks after lunch</title>
      <link>http://oliviaweng.github.io/blog/lunch-walks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 16:57:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oliviaweng.github.io/blog/lunch-walks/</guid>
      <description>Dear reader, Taking walks after lunch, mostly alone but occasionally with friends, has been one of the best decisions I&#39;ve made in college. I used to approach college with a keep-your-foot-on-the-gas-for-the-love-of-all-that-is-good mentality. Not working was bad and a waste of time. Then the unsustainability of it all hit me around my third year. It was only halfway through the year, and I woke up every day feeling burned out, worn out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://oliviaweng.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oliviaweng.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&#39;m Olivia. I&#39;m a second-year PhD student in Computer Science working with Professor Ryan Kastner at UC San Diego. My research centers on computer architecture, focusing on end-of-Moore&#39;s-Law computing vis-à-vis hardware acceleration.
Before coming to UCSD, I received my BS in Computer Science at the University of Chicago, where I worked with Professor Yanjing Li on mitigating cache side-channel attacks while maintaining cache performance and Professor Andrew A. Chien on integrating SSD latency predictors into cloud systems via hardware accelerators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://oliviaweng.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://oliviaweng.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>ResNet Reshaper: Reshaping Residual Networks for Resource-Efficient Inference on FPGAs Residual networks (ResNets) employ skip connections in their networks&amp;mdash;reusing activations from previous layers&amp;mdash;to improve training convergence, but these skip connections create challenges for hardware implementations of ResNets. In particular, they are problematic for inference accelerators on resource-limited platforms because they introduce a bottleneck during inference: the layers whose activations are reused in future layers must wait for this reuse to occur before accepting new input and continuing to compute.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>